Goodbye, boss.
안녕히 계세요, 보스.
See you tomorrow.
내일 봐요.
I'm leaving first, brother.
나 먼저 갈게, 형.
goodbye.
안녕히 가세요.
Mr. and Mrs.
씨와 부인
Auntie is back.
이모가 돌아왔다.
Why did you come suddenly?
갑자기 왜 오셨어요?
Isn't this
이거 아닌가?
my colleagues
나의 동료
give me one
하나 줘 봐
I don't smoke.
나는 담배를 피우지 않습니다.
I brought it to you.
내가 가져왔어.
Last year the doctor told me
작년에 의사가 나한테 말했지
Quit smoking and drinking.
흡연과 음주를 중단하십시오.
I've been using it for a few months
나는 그것을 몇 달 동안 사용해 왔습니다.
no more smoking
더 이상 담배를 피우지 마세요
That's good
좋아요
You are not a fishing law enforcement officer
귀하는 낚시법 집행관이 아닙니다.
Is it right to test me?
나를 시험하는 것이 옳은가?
I did not mean that
그것을 의미 한게 아닌데
But honestly
하지만 솔직히
Quitting smoking is not easy.
담배를 끊는 것은 쉽지 않습니다.
You must survive.
당신은 살아남아야합니다.
Are you still quitting candy?
아직도 사탕 끊으세요?
I bought you more.
나는 당신을 더 샀다.
more
더
Huang Zicheng bought so many for me
황쯔쳉이 나한테 너무 많이 사줬어
I haven't eaten much lately
최근에 많이 먹지 않았어
No purchase required.
구매가 필요하지 않습니다.
You haven't eaten yet?
아직 식사 안 하셨나요?
I definitely haven’t eaten it yet.
물론 아직 먹어본 적은 없습니다.
I shouldn't ask
묻지 말아야지
I'll cook for you
내가 요리해줄게
Noodles are pretty good
국수는 꽤 괜찮습니다
Oh yes.
바로 이거 야.
In that white porcelain jar
저 백자 항아리 속에
It’s this year’s new tea.
올해 새로 나온 차예요.
Mix it yourself.
직접 섞어보세요.
OK
좋아요
What is the word?
단어는 무엇입니까?
I'll invite you out to dinner.
저녁 식사에 당신을 초대하겠습니다.
I found a new restaurant.
새로운 식당을 찾았어요.
good.
좋은.
next time
다음번
Wait for Zicheng to come back
Zicheng이 돌아올 때까지 기다리세요
let's go together
같이 가자
you can also.
당신은 또한 수.
Fried noodles.
볶음면.
OK
좋아요
People have already arranged it.
사람들은 이미 그것을 준비했습니다.
5.30pm.
오후 5시 30분
In the town square,
마을 광장에서는
[In the town square. ]
[마을 광장에서. ]
Can he recognize me?
그 사람이 나를 알아볼 수 있을까?
He only knows things, not people.
그는 사물만 알고 사람은 모릅니다.
OK
좋아요
5.30pm.
오후 5시 30분
In the town square.
마을 광장에서.
I doubt him
나는 그를 의심한다
There is important information about biological companies.
바이오 회사에 관한 중요한 정보가 있습니다.
Biological groups?
생물학적 그룹?
of.
의.
Shi Tou, gambar.
Shi Tou, 감바르.
The target has emerged.
타겟이 나왔습니다.
understand.
이해하다.
The target entered the milk tea shop.
타겟은 밀크티 가게에 들어갔습니다.
Enter your payment code here.
여기에 결제 코드를 입력하세요.
OK
좋아요
How are you? This is a receipt for you.
잘 지내세요? 당신을 위한 영수증입니다.
Thanks.
감사해요.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
give me a cup of black tea
나에게 홍차 한 잔 주세요
OK
좋아요
Hello, please scan the QR code to pay.
안녕하세요. 결제하시려면 QR코드를 스캔해주세요.
Parson is here.
파슨이 여기 있어요.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Hello, I would like a glass of orange juice.
안녕하세요, 오렌지 주스 한 잔 주세요.
Another cake.
또 다른 케이크.
wrap.
포장하다.
OK
좋아요
Hello, please scan the QR code to pay.
안녕하세요. 결제하시려면 QR코드를 스캔해주세요.
attention.
주목.
A new stranger.
새로운 낯선 사람.
Director Qin.
진 감독.
The connection target has been determined.
연결 대상이 결정되었습니다.
But the circumstances surrounding the transfer of the goods are unclear.
그러나 물품 양도를 둘러싼 정황은 불분명하다.
We have to pay attention to who is coming.
누가 오는지 주목해야 합니다.
After leaving the market,
시장을 나온 후,
After leaving the market.
시장을 떠난 후.
Don't lose him.
그를 잃지 마세요.
Where is the courier?
택배는 어디에 있나요?
If so, the sender will not move first
그렇다면 보낸 사람이 먼저 움직이지 않을 것입니다.
Just pay attention.
주의하세요.
understand.
이해하다.
Someone is following you.
누군가가 당신을 따라오고 있습니다.
Enter the mall.
쇼핑몰에 들어가세요.
You have become a target.
당신은 표적이 되었습니다.
WHO？
WHO?
For example, the National Security Agency.
예를 들어, 국가 안보국.
The goods must not fall into Guo An's hands.
물품이 궈안의 손에 들어가서는 안 됩니다.
Target lost.
목표가 사라졌습니다.
sun
해
The sender suddenly disappeared.
보낸 사람이 갑자기 사라졌습니다.
Pay attention to the recipient.
받는 사람에게 주의를 기울이십시오.
The goods are in his hands
물건은 그의 손에 있다
I doubt they've noticed
나는 그들이 눈치챘을지 의심스럽다
The consignee is ready to go out.
수취인이 나갈 준비가 되었습니다.
Ada Guo An.
에이다 구오 안.
where to.
어디로.
The item is missing.
항목이 누락되었습니다.
Jiang.
장.
Supervise consignees.
수취인을 감독합니다.
why you again
왜 또 너야?
Let me go.
가자.
Everyone across the country is safe.
전국의 모든 분들이 안전하십니다.
You can't go out anymore.
더 이상 나갈 수 없습니다.
I must go.
나는 가야만 한다.
if not,
그렇지 않다면,
complete you
당신을 완성하다
You can't leave here with your stuff.
당신은 당신의 물건을 가지고 여기를 떠날 수 없습니다.
Just change your clothes and leave.
옷만 갈아입고 나가시면 됩니다.
Give me that thing.
그거 주세요.
There's no use them arresting you.
그들이 당신을 체포해도 아무 소용이 없습니다.
They'll see you soon.
곧 뵙겠습니다.
Time is running out.
시간이 얼마 남지 않았습니다.
Where is that thing?
그거 어디 있지?
you are right.
당신 말이 맞아요.
The item is missing.
항목이 누락되었습니다.
It's no use for them to catch me.
그들이 나를 잡아도 소용이 없습니다.
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
before i know
내가 알기도 전에
who betrayed me
누가 나를 배신했나
It's possible for anyone
누구에게나 가능하다
Go north.
북쪽으로 가세요.
Where are the people?
사람들은 어디에 있나요?
Already published
이미 게시됨
Where is this item?
이 항목은 어디에 있나요?
It was ruined.
그것은 망가졌습니다.
Gao Ke
가오 케
The recipient of the shipment has been controlled.
배송 수령인이 통제되었습니다.
Well, I'll go now
자, 이제 갈게요
Do you see what's inside?
안에 무엇이 있는지 보이나요?
It should be a sample.
샘플이어야합니다.
In biological companies,
생물학 회사에서는
There are indeed nails.
실제로 손톱이 있습니다.
You let him go on purpose again.
당신은 그를 의도적으로 다시 놓아주었습니다.
catch him.
그를 잡아.
He won't tell anyone.
그는 아무에게도 말하지 않을 것입니다.
He still doesn't believe you.
그 사람은 아직도 당신을 믿지 않아요.
Not that easy.
그렇게 쉽지는 않습니다.
How to make a head start
먼저 시작하는 방법
See us?
우리를 볼까요?
I guess
내 생각엔
beside him
그 옆에
spy
스파이
This is our negligence
이건 우리의 부주의야
How was it exposed?
어떻게 노출됐나요?
have no idea.
전혀 모른다.
your identity
당신의 정체성
Only Gao Tian knows
오직 Gao Tian만이 알고 있다
he let me go
그 사람이 날 놓아줬어
Where are the samples?
샘플은 어디에 있나요?
It was ruined.
그것은 망가졌습니다.
sample.
견본.
Don't fall into Guo An's hands.
Guo An의 손에 빠지지 마십시오.
Now, he's your ace.
이제 그는 당신의 에이스입니다.
You must protect him.
당신은 그를 보호해야합니다.
I know.
알아요.
Bassoon.
바순.
He is a sailor.
그는 선원입니다.
Code car driver.
코드 자동차 운전사.
Responsible for sending information.
정보를 전달하는 역할을 담당합니다.
but he doesn't know
하지만 그 사람은 몰라
About Jin Hai’s condition.
진하이의 상태에 대해서.
He is just a courier
그 사람은 그냥 택배기사야
Our goal
우리의 목표
It's a big hidden fish
숨어있는 큰 물고기예요
In Bio Group.
바이오그룹에 있습니다.
I warned you.
나는 당신에게 경고했다.
Stop looking for trouble.
문제를 찾지 마세요.
Someone doubted me.
누군가 나를 의심했습니다.
Your female colleague?
당신의 여자 동료?
before you act,
행동하기 전에,
You'd better tell me first.
나한테 먼저 말씀해 주시는 게 좋을 것 같아요.
I can't save you every time.
매번 당신을 구할 수는 없습니다.
Go to the department head.
부서장에게 가십시오.
Why do I think so?
왜 그렇게 생각합니까?
look
바라보다
every move of mine
나의 모든 움직임
Because you have a problem,
당신에게 문제가 있기 때문에,
I'm going to be in trouble.
나는 곤경에 처할 것이다.
That's fine if you think so.
그렇게 생각하시면 괜찮습니다.
Asking questions, this time it’s the National Security Bureau
질문을 던진다 이번에는 국가안전보위부다
How do you know we've met?
우리가 만난 걸 어떻게 알죠?
we got the message
우리는 메시지를 받았습니다
car driver
자동차 운전자
Yakabus members enter the country.
야카부스 회원들이 입국합니다.
I suspect he's here to get information.
내 생각엔 그가 정보를 얻으려고 여기에 온 것 같아요.
We've been watching him for a long time.
우리는 오랫동안 그를 지켜봐왔습니다.
I didn't realize you were the one who sent the message.
메시지를 보낸 사람이 당신인 줄 몰랐어요.
I can not
나는 할 수 없다
I can't find a weakness.
약점을 못찾겠어요
Since Yaoqie doesn’t trust me,
Yaoqie가 나를 믿지 않기 때문에
You don’t have to look for me anymore
더 이상 나를 찾지 않아도 돼
They can't find you.
그들은 당신을 찾을 수 없습니다.
Can I?
할 수 있나요?
I want to believe you.
나는 당신을 믿고 싶다.
What about the man you trust?
당신이 신뢰하는 남자는 어떻습니까?
Do you want me to cook for you?
내가 당신을 위해 요리해 줄까요?
You helped me today.
오늘 저를 도와주셨어요.
I haven't thanked you yet.
나는 아직 당신에게 감사를 표하지 않았습니다.
at your side,
네 편에서,
bukan Xiao Yi saja, kan?
부칸 Xiao Yi 사자, 칸?
certainly.
틀림없이.
But I'm not as good as you.
하지만 나는 당신만큼 좋지 않습니다.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
I don't like sharing with others
나는 다른 사람과 공유하는 것을 좋아하지 않는다
Another girl
다른 여자
You don't gossip
당신은 험담하지 않습니다
This is a sponsor
후원자입니다
I'm here to buy
나는 구매하러 왔습니다
The material in Crow's hand.
크로우의 손에 있는 재료.
I asked him out
나는 그에게 데이트 신청을 했다
ask him out
그에게 물어봐
he gave it to me
그 사람이 나한테 줬어
He gave it to me.
그는 나에게 그것을 주었다.
This is this time
이번이야말로
Boss, be generous.
사장님, 관대하세요.
Wu Senlin
우센린
people with background
배경을 가진 사람들
please sign in.
로그인 해주세요.
Gentlemen.
신사.
Please come up.
올라오세요.
The materials in Crow's hands are quite popular.
크로우의 손에 있는 재료들은 꽤 인기가 있다.
Sources say a buyer has been found.
소식통에 따르면 구매자가 발견되었다고 합니다.
if not for
그렇지 않다면
owe me a favor
나에게 빚을 졌다
he won't face me
그 사람은 나한테 얼굴을 대지 않을 거야
Found a buyer.
구매자를 찾았습니다.
of.
의.
It is understood that he has already paid the deposit.
이미 보증금을 지불한 것으로 알려졌다.
He's inside.
그는 안에 있어요.
speak slowly
천천히 말하다
sit down.
앉아.
that's right.
좋아요.
Someone paid a deposit
누군가가 보증금을 지불했습니다.
Want to chat more?
더 많은 이야기를 나누고 싶으십니까?
yes?
예?
Two days ago,
이틀 전,
Looks like what's in your hand
손에 들고 있는게 보이는데
it's not easy
쉽지 않다
certainly.
틀림없이.
If we offer a higher price,
더 높은 가격을 제안한다면,
Can we
우리는 할 수 있습니까?
No matter how high the price is, it can’t be sold.
가격이 아무리 높아도 팔 수 없습니다.
This is the rule.
이것이 규칙입니다.
Please next time
다음에도 부탁드려요
We had the opportunity to work together.
우리는 함께 일할 기회를 가졌습니다.
OK
좋아요
I also want to search
나도 검색하고 싶다
stable buyer
안정적인 구매자
It's easy and safe.
쉽고 안전합니다.
of.
의.
But how can I be sure
하지만 어떻게 확신할 수 있나요?
Materials in your hand
당신의 손에 있는 재료
Only sell to me.
나한테만 팔아요.
I said,
나는 말했다,
Business activities must abide by the rules.
사업 활동은 규칙을 준수해야 합니다.
If not later
나중에 안되면
Neither will anyone else
다른 사람도 마찬가지일 것이다
Buy something from me.
나한테서 뭔가를 사세요.
In the world of agents
에이전트의 세계에서는
There are no rules.
규칙이 없습니다.
Offline transactions
오프라인 거래
Eliminate face-to-face copying
대면 복사 제거
is the safest.
가장 안전합니다.
impossible.
불가능한.
i won't see you
난 당신을 볼 수 없습니다
agent game
에이전트 게임
It is the safest trading market
가장 안전한 거래시장입니다
If you don't accept it,
받아들이지 않으면,
We can no longer work together.
우리는 더 이상 함께 일할 수 없습니다.
Be your buyer this time
이번에는 구매자가 되어 보세요
Do you accept online transactions?
온라인 거래를 허용합니까?
certainly.
틀림없이.
who is he?
그는 누구입니까?
Is he a philosophy student?
그 사람 철학과 학생인가요?
This has nothing to do with you.
이것은 당신과 아무 관련이 없습니다.
If he is a person who studies philosophy,
철학을 공부하는 사람이라면,
your transaction
귀하의 거래
It won't be that easy.
그렇게 쉬운 일은 아닐 겁니다.
He will cause you trouble.
그는 당신에게 문제를 일으킬 것입니다.
Have a question for me?
나에게 질문이 있나요?
He might find you.
그 사람이 당신을 찾을 수도 있어요.
Do you know where I am?
내가 어디에 있는지 아세요?
Have you read Jae-chul
재철님 읽어보셨나요?
who are you?
누구세요?
I'm here for
나는 여기에 있습니다
with you
너와 함께
but i care more
하지만 난 더 관심이 있어
your safety
당신의 안전
You are not here to trade.
당신은 거래하러 온 것이 아닙니다.
do not waste time.
시간을 낭비하지 마십시오.
How can you be sure?
어떻게 확신할 수 있나요?
He reads Jae Cheol's works
재철 작가의 작품을 읽는다
I wasn't sure before this
이 전에는 확신이 없었어요
But his earlier response
하지만 그의 초기 반응은
In principle it is certain.
원칙적으로는 확실합니다.
He can still go out now
그 사람은 지금도 밖에 나갈 수 있어
significance
중요성
He is safe for now.
그는 지금은 안전합니다.
We can find Jae-chul reading a book
책을 읽고 있는 재철이 보이네요
Even the Nightmist can do it.
Nightmist조차도 그것을 할 수 있습니다.
So his current situation
그래서 그의 현재 상황은
very dangerous.
매우 위험한.
We must find him immediately.
즉시 그를 찾아야 해요.
Many people are reading philosophy books.
많은 사람들이 철학 서적을 읽고 있습니다.
How to find it?
그것을 찾는 방법?
I heard your conversation didn't go well.
대화가 잘 안 된다고 들었습니다.
what did he say?
그는 무엇을 말 했는가?
He said you were insincere
그 사람은 당신이 성실하지 않다고 하더군요
and wanted to deceive him
그를 속이고 싶었어
no
아니요
Tauke Wu
타우케 우
Want to deal with him offline
오프라인에서 그 사람을 상대하고 싶나요?
he doesn't agree
그 사람은 동의하지 않아
this game
이 게임
Who wants to reveal something?
누가 뭔가를 공개하고 싶나요?
one's true identity
자신의 진정한 정체성
after all,
결국,
He still lives with leaks
그는 아직도 누수를 안고 살아요
I found you
나는 당신을 찾았습니다
quite profitable
꽤 수익성이 좋다
When did you recommend me?
언제 추천하셨나요?
Are you still going to your hacker league?
아직도 해커 리그에 가시나요?
It's enough.
충분 해.
Be careful the police will find you.
경찰이 당신을 찾을 수 있으니 조심하세요.
Oh yes.
바로 이거 야.
Usually, he works for the same company.
보통 그는 같은 회사에서 일한다.
How long does he work?
그 사람은 얼마나 일해요?
The time is short, one or two years.
시간은 1~2년 정도로 짧다.
If it is slow, it may take more than three years.
느리면 3년 이상 걸릴 수도 있다.
See when he
그 사람이 언제인지 봐
Get the material he wants.
그가 원하는 자료를 얻으세요.
OK
좋아요
Me too
저도요
Offend your friends.
친구들을 화나게하십시오.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
Decide to start a business
창업을 결심하다
There is no separation.
분리가 없습니다.
I like this girl.
나는 이 여자를 좋아한다.
How do you know I'm a girl?
내가 여자인 걸 어떻게 알죠?
we are best friends.
우리는 최고의 친구 다.
You hate it.
당신은 그것을 싫어합니다.
she's just a girl
그 사람은 그냥 여자야
Thanks.
감사해요.
I'll call you next time.
다음에 전화할게요.
OK
좋아요
Come on, miss.
어서, 아가씨.
I know how to investigate.
조사하는 방법을 알고 있습니다.
Speech.
연설.
look.
바라보다.
He got important information
그는 중요한 정보를 얻었습니다
and find a buyer.
그리고 구매자를 찾으세요.
The next step is
다음 단계는
Resign and get out of here.
사임하고 여기서 나가세요.
your previous question
이전 질문
It must be interesting
재미있겠군요
his attention.
그의 관심.
He will go faster.
그는 더 빨리 갈 것입니다.
make sense.
말이 되네요.
I think
제 생각에는
we can try
우리는 시도 할 수 있습니다
Ask Yaoyao for help.
야오야오에게 도움을 요청하세요.
Yao Yao
야오야오
he is reading
그는 책을 읽고 있다
Ask him to help investigate this person
이 사람을 조사하는 데 도움을 달라고 요청하세요
No, Yaoyao can't.
아니요, Yaoyao는 그럴 수 없습니다.
His status is not suitable for intervention
그의 상태는 개입하기에 적합하지 않습니다
We suspect someone
우리는 누군가를 의심한다
There is night fog.
밤안개가 있습니다.
our investigation
우리의 조사
It must be done in secret.
그것은 비밀리에 이루어져야 합니다.
How do we investigate?
어떻게 조사하나요?
hunter.
사냥꾼.
Hunting companies dominate
사냥 회사가 지배적이다
All resignation information
모든 퇴직 정보
and information about employees who are resigning.
그리고 퇴사하는 직원에 관한 정보.
we can pass
우리는 통과할 수 있다
through this channel
이 채널을 통해
Awesome, Sister Xi
대단해요, 시 자매님
give it to me.
그걸 나에게주세요.
I know people from hunting companies.
나는 사냥 회사 출신의 사람들을 알고 있습니다.
Why does everyone know each other?
왜 다들 서로 아는 사이야?
when i graduate,
내가 졸업 할 때,
With my excellent experience,
나의 탁월한 경험으로,
[My resume is outstanding. ]
[내 이력서가 훌륭해요. ]
invite
초대하다
Finally I refused.
마침내 나는 거절했다.
Don't you want to be blacklisted?
블랙리스트에 오르고 싶지 않으신가요?
Don't worry.
괜찮아요.
not like this.
이건 아니야.
split in trade
무역 분할
We also have people in our hunting company
우리 사냥대에도 사람이 있어요
If you are so proactive
너무 적극적이라면
I can only suspect that you have other motives.
나는 당신에게 다른 동기가 있다고 의심할 뿐입니다.
I do this to...
나는 이것을하기 위해 ...
For national security.
국가 안보를 위해.
You do this for someone.
당신은 누군가를 위해 이 일을 합니다.
small.
작은.
If you think of it this way, the pattern is very small.
이렇게 생각하면 패턴이 매우 작습니다.
I go first, you run
내가 먼저 가 넌 달려
Don't run away, bye.
도망가지 마세요, 안녕.
I left the keys at home.
열쇠를 집에 두고 왔습니다.
I will go to your house.
나는 당신 집에 갈 것이다.
My house is a mess. Only next time.
우리 집은 엉망이에요. 다음 번에만.
You are looking for an important company.
당신은 중요한 회사를 찾고 있습니다.
My car is here, I'm leaving first.
내 차가 여기 있으니 나 먼저 출발할게.
Why can't we leave after we break up?
우리는 왜 헤어지고 나면 떠날 수 없는 걸까요?
Geshe
게셰
from hunter
사냥꾼에게서
Latest information received
최신 정보 수신
Newest
최신
include
포함하다
who is ready to resign
사임할 준비가 되어 있는 사람
and intends to resign
그리고 사임할 예정이다
and their resume.
그리고 그들의 이력서.
Also inside.
또한 내부.
I sent you an email.
난 너에게 이메일을 보냈어.
Thanks.
감사해요.
The job is done.
작업이 완료되었습니다.
wake up.
깨우다.
Can't sleep well
잠을 잘 못 자요
I don't go to bed until four o'clock
나는 4시가 될 때까지 잠자리에 들지 않는다
I changed my bag again today
오늘 또 가방을 바꿨어요
Is this beautiful?
이게 아름다운가요?
limited edition
한정판
I don't want to buy it.
나는 그것을 사고 싶지 않습니다.
I will regret it for a year.
1년 동안 후회할 거예요.
During this year,
올해 동안,
only a meager salary
단지 월급이 적다
I’ve bought a bag, what do you want to eat?
한 봉지 샀는데 뭐 먹을래?
I eat you
나는 너를 먹는다
If I don't have money,
돈이 없으면,
You can't see me starving
내가 굶주리는 걸 볼 수는 없잖아
Don't count on it.
그것에 의존하지 마십시오.
I checked yesterday.
어제 확인했어요.
Last few years,
지난 몇 년간,
some scandal
약간의 스캔들
on other internet platforms.
다른 인터넷 플랫폼에서.
some people
어떤 사람들은
thereby leaking user privacy
이로 인해 사용자 개인정보가 유출됩니다.
And those who fake clicks
그리고 가짜 클릭을 하는 사람들
Who deliberately manipulates the topic.
의도적으로 주제를 조작하는 사람.
They have one thing in common.
그들은 한 가지 공통점을 가지고 있습니다.
There must be someone
누군가가 있을 거에요
into them
그들 속으로
from a technical point of view
기술적인 관점에서
From a technical perspective.
기술적 관점에서.
In fact, it's a scandal
사실 스캔들이에요
In the end the truth was not revealed.
결국 진실은 밝혀지지 않았다.
Everything will end.
모든 것이 끝날 것입니다.
you think
당신 생각에는
This time our crisis
이번에 우리의 위기
Not one thing.
한 가지도 아닙니다.
But done by the same group.
그런데 같은 그룹이 한 거예요.
they use the same method
그들은 같은 방법을 사용한다
Also used to threaten other platforms
다른 플랫폼을 위협하는데도 사용됨
and succeeded.
성공했습니다.
if
만약에
As I expected,
예상했던 대로,
Then this guy
그럼 이 사람
maybe once
아마 한 번은
In some iQiyi.
일부 iQiyi에서는.
continue.
계속하다.
I investigated Shi Qi's information.
Shi Qi의 정보를 조사했습니다.
He has worked for Company A for two years.
그는 A회사에서 2년 동안 근무했습니다.
During this period,
이 기간 동안,
The company has also had its share of scandals.
이 회사는 또한 스캔들에 휩싸였습니다.
According to the resume,
이력서에 따르면,
Shi Qi.
시 치.
Indeed he was suspected.
실제로 그는 의심을 받았습니다.
if it's not the first time
처음이 아니라면
do something like this,
이런 짓을 해라,
It turns out
그것은 밝혀
he made a lot of money
그는 돈을 많이 벌었어요
through this channel
이 채널을 통해
so
그래서
his financial status
그의 재정 상태
Absolutely good
정말 좋아요
But look, Principal Zhou
그런데 보세요, 저우 교장 선생님
him on the address page
그 사람 주소 페이지에
Full of ordinary neighborhoods.
평범한 동네가 가득합니다.
Although I have never been to his house
비록 나는 그 사람 집에 가본 적이 없지만
But I searched online.
그런데 온라인으로 검색해 봤습니다.
The area is quite remote
지역이 꽤 멀다
The rent is also cheap.
임대료도 저렴해요.
After all, he is not rich
결국 그는 부자가 아니다
He is not a rich man.
그는 부자가 아닙니다.
Could it be him
그 사람이 아닐까?
deliberately hidden
의도적으로 숨긴
own money
자신의 돈
Who are you
누구세요
The son of the invisible millionaire
보이지 않는 백만장자의 아들
There is a mine at home.
집에 광산이 있습니다.
I admit
나는 인정한다
imitate
본뜨다
is that true
그게 사실인가요?
This work is quite good
이 작품 꽤 괜찮네요
Yes, I think so too.
그래요. 저도 그렇게 생각 해요.
Can't see this
이것을 볼 수 없습니다
Later you refused to give me this land
나중에 너희는 나에게 이 땅을 주기를 거부했다
Yes.
예.
no problem
괜찮아요
what do you think?
어떻게 생각하나요?
He always buys luxury goods.
그는 항상 명품을 구입한다.
But he told me,
하지만 그는 나에게 이렇게 말했습니다.
all fake.
모두 가짜.
The conversation still needs to be discussed.
대화는 여전히 논의되어야 합니다.
But I think,
하지만 나는 생각해,
You can continue to investigate
계속 조사할 수 있습니다.
Continue to investigate
계속 조사
if necessary
필요하다면
Use a little trick.
약간의 트릭을 사용하십시오.
For example
예를 들어
For example, record a conversation
예를 들어 대화를 녹음하세요.
Or the reality of his family.
아니면 그의 가족의 현실.
this...
이것...
You are a friend.
당신은 친구입니다.
It doesn't seem difficult to you.
당신에게는 어렵지 않은 것 같습니다.
Yao Yao.
야오야오.
I know you.
나는 당신을 알고 있습니다.
Don't you want to know?
알고 싶지 않으세요?
what friends do you have
당신은 어떤 친구가 있나요?
for you?
당신을 위한?
OK
좋아요
Let me try.
나 해보자.
Why?
왜?
I want to change my job.
직업을 바꾸고 싶습니다.
Why suddenly?
왜 갑자기?
what happen?
무슨 일이야?
It has been a long time.
오랜 시간이 걸렸습니다.
The hunter dug me out.
사냥꾼이 나를 파헤쳤어요.
My heart was pounding.
내 심장이 쿵쾅거렸다.
Which company do you want to go to?
어느 회사에 가고 싶나요?
Three major game companies
3대 게임회사
I have not decided yet.
나는 아직 결정하지 못했다.
Have you mentioned it to the staff?
직원에게 말했나요?
of.
의.
No, you've thought about it
아니, 생각해 봤잖아
you make a decision
당신은 결정을 내린다
Just leave me like this?
날 이대로 그냥 내버려둬?
You want to go to your boss
당신은 상사에게 가고 싶어
I'm bored living here.
나는 여기서 사는 것이 지루해요.
But some of these companies
하지만 이들 회사 중 일부는
Everything is nearby.
모든 것이 근처에 있습니다.
We can play together again.
우리는 다시 함께 놀 수 있어요.
Si Qi.
시 치.
Let's sign autographs.
사인을 해보자.
Geshe
게셰
between them,
그들 사이에,
i know someone
나는 누군가를 알고 있다
Zhou Si Qi?
저우시치?
of.
의.
He is Yaoyao's best friend.
그는 Yaoyao의 가장 친한 친구입니다.
I've investigated
나는 조사했다
his past
그의 과거
you don't speak
당신은 말을하지 않습니다
Very similar indeed
정말 매우 비슷해요
We've checked.
우리는 확인했습니다.
The best person for Crow's situation.
크로우의 상황에 가장 적합한 사람.
So does he.
그도 마찬가지다.
but...
하지만...
He is not a crow.
그는 까마귀가 아닙니다.
why is it impossible
왜 불가능합니까?
Jiang Xiaohua reminded me
장샤오화(Jiang Xiaohua)가 나에게 상기시켜 주었다
hacker
해커
Can be disguised
위장 가능
own identity.
자신의 정체성.
I was surprised he was a crow.
나는 그가 까마귀라는 것에 놀랐다.
Have you had any contact with him?
그 사람과 연락한 적 있어요?
No.
아니요.
But isn't he?
하지만 그 사람은 아닌가요?
Yaoyao's best friend?
야오야오의 가장 친한 친구?
Before that, I always heard Yao Ming mention him.
그 전에는 야오밍이 그에 대해 언급하는 걸 늘 들었어요.
you say
당신은 말한다
Yaoyao's identity, he
야오야오의 정체성, 그는
Why is it so complicated?
왜 그렇게 복잡합니까?
OK
좋아요
We'll take care of the rest.
나머지는 우리가 처리하겠습니다.
What should I do next?
다음에 무엇을 해야 합니까?
continue working.
계속 일하세요.
If anything happens I will contact you.
무슨 일이 생기면 연락드리겠습니다.
Are you leaving me again?
또 날 떠나는 거야?
of course not
당연히 아니지
your abilities in the game
게임에서의 당신의 능력
Really helped us.
정말로 우리에게 도움이 되었습니다.
Geshe
게셰
You are more loyal than Gao Tianyang.
당신은 Gao Tianyang보다 더 충성 스럽습니다.
I'll tell him on your behalf.
내가 당신을 대신해서 그에게 말할게요.
goodbye.
안녕히 가세요.
Shi Qi will resign.
Shi Qi가 사임합니다.
I know.
알아요.
This is no coincidence, right?
이건 우연이 아니죠?
The goal has been achieved.
목표가 달성되었습니다.
Definitely need to be ready to go.
반드시 갈 준비가 되어 있어야 합니다.
I've looked into it.
나는 그것을 조사했다.
his bag
그의 가방
it is true.
그건 진실이야.
It seems that he deliberately concealed it
일부러 숨긴거 같은데
own financial ability.
자신의 재정적 능력.
Now it seems
이제는 것 같다
Mr. Zhou, you are right
저우 씨, 당신 말이 맞아요
I might
어쩌면
don't understand him
그를 이해하지 못한다
his address
그의 주소
is fake.
가짜입니다.
please let me investigate
제가 조사하게 해주세요
where does he live
그는 어디에서 사니
OK
좋아요
Look for opportunities.
기회를 찾으십시오.
I'll go see it with him
내가 그 사람이랑 보러 갈게
Don't let him notice.
그 사람이 눈치채지 못하게 하세요.
Be careful.
조심하세요.
if there is nothing
아무것도 없다면
I go first.
내가 먼저 간다.
Go to work.
일하러 가다.
I found someone who asked me to investigate.
나에게 조사를 요청한 사람을 찾았습니다.
soon
곧
Yaoyao is very smart
야오야오는 정말 똑똑해요
You just sent it to him
방금 그 사람한테 보냈잖아
In order to attract Huang Zicheng,
황자성을 유치하기 위해
it's useless
그건 소용 없어
useless
쓸모 없는
Neither can Mr. Yu
유 씨도 마찬가지다.
at your place
당신의 집에서
but a smart man
하지만 똑똑한 사람
Usually not very obedient.
일반적으로 그다지 순종적이지 않습니다.
I will educate him well.
나는 그를 잘 교육시킬 것이다.
Bagi Zhou Si Qi,
Bagi Zhou Si Qi,
Please take care of me, Boss Zhang.
장보스님, 저를 잘 돌봐주세요.
take it out
그것을 꺼내
In his hands.
그의 손에.
Don't worry.
괜찮아요.
I'll take care of it.
내가 처리할게.
That's very good.
아주 좋습니다.
You repeat what he said.
당신은 그가 말한 것을 반복합니다.
useless
쓸모 없는
Neither can Mr. Yu
유 씨도 마찬가지다.
at your place
당신의 집에서
but a smart man
하지만 똑똑한 사람
Usually not very obedient.
일반적으로 그다지 순종적이지 않습니다.
Don't worry.
괜찮아요.
I'll take care of it.
내가 처리할게.
Just to name a few such poems
그런 시 몇 편을 꼽자면
of.
의.
So incomplete.
그래서 불완전합니다.